I heard from my mom
that you said you want to give me your heart.
What are you trying to get me to do?
Kill you so that I can live?
What are you trying to make me do?
No. I don't want it.
I'd rather die. I don't want it!
I came to tell you that.
Why don't you want it?
It's not like I'm dying for you.
I'm going to die regardless.
I want to do something good and end up in heaven.
Why? Are you jealous of that as well?
Then give it to someone else.
Why me?
Why does it have to be me?
Because I'm your brother.
You're my little brother, and I'm your big brother.
What are you saying?
I am your older brother.
I was born from the same mother.
I'm your brother brought into the world
by the same person.
If there's one difference between us,
it's that my twin sister and I
were abandoned when we were babies.
As if we were trash.
So stop throwing tantrums and go.
I'm too exhausted to tolerate your tantrums.
[Episode 14]
Mom, that's cheating.
No! You're cheating.
- No! Mom, you cheated.
- You cheated.
- I saw it.
What is this?
Rock flinging. You played with me once, remember?
Mom! Don't use your whole hand!
You can only use two fingers!
You did it with four fingers a while ago.
Move aside, Seo-kyeong. I'll win for you.
What did you bet? Hot buns?
Yeah.
Okay! Attack, Kim Galchi.
That's so unfair.
Two adults against one child?
My turn.
- Hey! It's Choi Yun!.
- What are you doing? I did it.
Oh, Choi Yun! Choi Yun! Choi Yun!
- Kim Galchi, it's your turn.
- What did you mean by that?
My mom gave birth to you and your sister
and abandoned you?
Are you telling me to believe that?
I don't get what you're trying to say right now.
Galchi, since we have a guest,
will you go make some tea?
Okay.
Seo-kyeong, go and help Galchi out.
How could that be?
That makes no sense at all.
I don't have much time left to live.
It's too short a time to even
say things that make sense.
If you were me, on the verge of death,
would you talk nonsense?
I don't believe it.
Then don't.
Muhyeok.
If you can't believe it, then don't.
Why did you hide it until now?
"I'm your child."
"The child that you abandoned."
Why didn't you say that? Why hide it?
Do you know how it feels to get abandoned?
Being abandoned means it's over before it even started.
Even if you were to return, you'd never be welcomed.
Being a good son is never showing up at all.
That's what it means.
We're not wonderful like you.
One is a worthless gangster wannabe who
doesn't know how long he has left to live,
And the other is too stupid to understand the world.
Even so, we still have pride.
We still feel embarrassment.
I don't believe it.
It doesn't make sense.
You're my mom's son?
How can I believe that?
I don't believe it! I won't believe it!
If you don't want to believe it, then don't!
If you don't want to, then don't.
I will spend the rest of my life
believing that woman is my mother.
It's all I have left to live by.
So, if you're embarrassed, why did you return?
To get revenge.
I thought it was too unfair to go out that way.
I want revenge.
Oh, before I die I should call her.
Mother, to tell you the truth,
I'm the son you abandoned.
And I'm dying. For your oh-so-wonderful son.
To save the son you cherish,
your son who is trash will die.
For me, would you shed one-millionth of the tears
you shed for Yun, Mother?
I'm leaving.
Seo-kyeong.
Yes?
That guy is your little brother.
What?
The singer Choi Yun is also your brother.
Galchi, come here.
Between the singer Choi Yun or...
I mean... Between Uncle Choi Yun and me,
who's more handsome?
Is he cooler or am I?
How come you don't know how to lie?
It's going to be hard for you in the real world
when you grow up, Galchi.
Eunchae?
You're Eunchae, right?
Galchi? What are you doing here?
This is our house.
Let's go in. Uncle and Mom are both home.
Eunchae?
Uh... You see.
I was on my way home, but accidentally ended up here.
You weren't coming to our house?
No, I wasn't going to your house.
I wasn't going to your house, Galchi.
Eunchae?
I wasn't going to your house.
Sorry.
Eunchae...
Hot buns! Hot buns!
Here, Uncle. Have some.
Eunchae seems strange, Mom.
Did Jjangoo get caught by his mother?
Yeah.
Eunchae what?
- Did he get beat up a lot?
- Yeah.
Eunchae what?
Eunchae seems a little strange.
Did you see Eunchae?
Yeah. I saw her a while ago in front of our house.
Is she in front of the house right now?
No, she wasn't coming to our house.
She was going to her house,
but said she accidentally came here.
Eunchae? Eunchae?
Eunchae?
Sorry!
Blockhead? Are you okay?
Are you okay?
It's cold, huh?
It's so cold.
I wish it was snowing hard right now. That'd be great.
Mister.
What are you doing right now?
Why are you looking at the wall
and smiling to yourself so early in the morning?
Here. Yun's mom wanted you to bring the laptop.
Oh. Okay.
Blockhead?
Eunchae?
Uncle, what's wrong? What's wrong?
What's wrong? Did you eat too much too quickly?
Yeah.
You should have eaten slowly!
Here... Rinse out your mouth.
Did you see Eunchae yesterday?
Did Eunchae really come to our house?
Yes.
I couldn't find her.
I searched everywhere, but couldn't find her.
Eunchae is dating Choi Yun, right?
It said they were going to get married on TV.
Eunchae?
Blockhead?
Mister!
[Heart Disease]
This is too hard.
Why did Mr. Kang bring such difficult books?
The font is so small.
Yun, what is heart transplant in English? Huh? Huh?
In English? You don't know?
Huh? Why are you looking at me like that?
Do I have something on my face?
Don't work too hard, Mom.
Huh?
Don't work too hard to save me.
Yun, is something wrong?
If I'm meant to live, then I'll live somehow.
If I was meant to die, then I'll die somehow.
So don't work so hard, Mom.
Yun.
How can you say something like that
to your own mother?
Is that something a child would dare say to his mother?
Is that something to say to your mom?
If it'll save you, I'd do anything.
Anything in my power.
I can do anything. Okay? Fine?
If I take Muhyeok's heart and live,
would you be happy?
From now on, don't do anything.
Don't do anything.
I beg you. Please.
Don't do it.
Yun...
Eunchae?
What are you doing here?
Why aren't you coming inside?
Nothing. Nothing.
What do you mean nothing?
What's with that expression?
You look insane.
- Eunchae?
- It's nothing.
Eunchae.
♪ Dashing through the snow
In a one-horse open sleigh ♪
- ♪ O'er the fields we go ♪
- ♪ Jingle bells, jingle bells ♪
Seo-kyeong.
- Seo-kyeong.
- Hmm?
Who is Galchi's dad?
Galchi's dad.
Don't you know who Galchi's dad is?
I do know.
Where is he right now?
Don't know.
Seo-kyeong, you need to meet someone nice and marry.
My sister needs to meet a nice man
and marry before I go.
I'm going to marry you, Uncle.
Mom.
Really. I'm going to marry Uncle.
You cannot marry your own brother.
Why not?
You can't. You just can't.
I told you that last time.
What is wrong with you?
So frustrating!
Why not?
How can you marry your own brother, you idiot?
What have you spent doing all these years?
Even Galchi knows, but why don't you know?
How long are you going to live like this?
Don't you feel embarrassed in front of Galchi?
Don't you feel sorry?
Listen carefully.
Memorize things you are told
until your head explodes!
Galchi!
Why are you yelling at my mom?
You can just teach her over and over again!
You told me to keep on teaching her
if she doesn't know.
You said that to me,
so why are yelling at my mom?
Why are you yelling at my mom? You're really mean.
Mom, are you okay?
- Here.
- Yes, ma'am.
Lady!
Galchi's mom Oh, what's wrong?
What's wrong? Did you cry?
Why are you crying? What's wrong?
What's wrong? What's happening? Huh?
Uncle keeps yelling at me saying I'm stupid.
I don't know what your sister did wrong,
- But one shouldn't do that to their sister, right?
- Yes.
Your sister is sick.
- Take all of it back.
- Mr. Cha.
Take all of it back right now!
Mr. Cha. Obviously, there's been
a misunderstanding. The reason I came...
I told you I'd give it to you even
if you don't give me anything.
Even if you don't bring these,
even if you don't beg me,
I've told you already I'm going
to give it to you before I die!
Mr. Cha, seriously. You have me all wrong.
I came here with pure intentions...
Get out.
Mr. Cha.
Get out right now.
Take this and get out of my house!
Mr. Cha.
Get out!
You get out! If anyone goes, it should be you!
Why are you yelling at the pretty lady?
You thug.
If anyone goes, it should be you, you dummy.
Mom.
You're so mean?
This is my house, not yours.
If anyone goes, it should be you!
Mr. Cha.
Geez! That stupid jerk.
I wish I could show him how true my intentions are.
I really came here with completely pure intentions.
My Yun. He's been so fussy lately.
And I don't know how to explain it.
But Seo-kyeong and Galchi,
you two keep popping into my head...
You believe me, don't you, Seo-kyeong?
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
[Messages from fans:
"Are you okay, Yun?" "Get well soon, Yun]
This is a message from a 40-year-old female fan.
I'll read it.
"Hello, Choi Yun.
I'm a Buddhist monk.
I went to the temple to pray for your health yesterday.
I must have bowed a hundred times to Buddha yesterday.
I know it must be tough.
But always remember to have faith and courage."
If I give my heart to Yun, would you come to me?
"Even through hard times,
always love yourself till the end."
If I do one good thing before I die,
maybe I won't go to hell.
And it will be good for you, Yun, and Yun's mom.
Eunchae?
Yun, I'm going to step out for a while.
One minute.
I'll go out and come back in a minute.
Blockhead?
This is you, isn't it?
Eunchae? This is Eunchae, right?
How are you?
You're fine, right?
I'm doing great. I'm really healthy.
You're really okay, right?
Blockhead.
I missed you so much
I ran all the way here without stopping.
Pretty good, huh?
My little Blockhead,
you're definitely pretty when you smile.
Pretty soon, you'll be prettier than Ms. Australia.
Mister.
Eunchae?
What are you doing?
Who are you smiling at?
Mister?
Have you gone mad?
Have you finally lost it, Song Eunchae?
Muhyeok is not here.
Where do you see him?
Was it Muhyeok you saw and smiled at just now?
Was it?
No....
No, Yun.
Let's go inside.
Let's go in.
Hey, Sukchae.
Isn't Eunchae a bit strange lately?
Is Eunchae acting a bit weird?
Or saying weird things lately?
Eunchae is always strange.
For her to be acting normal is stranger to me.
Give it.
Yun, it's Minchae.
Eunchae was acting weird this morning.
By the gate, as if someone was there,
she was smiling at the wall.
Like crazy people, you know?
- She did that?
- Yup.
Yun?
It's cold. Don't come out.
- No. No.
- It's okay.
Seo-kyeong!
You make the best seaweed rolls in the world!
How do you do it?
You've made me forget all of the
stress I've built up due to Yun.
- I can come back again, right?
- Yeah!
Galchi. Don't be as mean to your mom
as my son's being to me, okay?
Okay.
Parents are the most
vulnerable people in the world.
And I think that people who are bad
to their parents are the worst.
Yeah.
I'm really going. Bye!
- Bye.
Eunchae?
Song Eunchae?
Come sit down.
Do you want to go to Muhyeok?
If you want, I'll let go of you.
But you can't go to Muhyeok.
Instead of Muhyeok,
tell me when you find someone else.
Then I'll let go.
Ah, I'm sleepy.
I think I should go to sleep.
I feel sleepy all of a sudden.
I won't be able to see you leave.
Bye.
[Choi Yun]
Do you remember what I said?
I said if there is nothing I could do for my woman,
I'd give her up.
I think that is what a man should do.
I called because of Eunchae.
Eunchae is going crazy.
I'm not kidding, seriously. Eunchae is going nuts.
We...
No, you and I have driven her insane.
It was better when we didn't do anything for her.
We are driving Eunchae insane.
I'll let her go. You let her go, too.
The only thing you can give to Eunchae is pain.
Please. Let her go.
No.
Taxi, taxi!
Blockhead.
Eunchae.
Have you gone mad?
Have you finally lost it, Song Eunchae?
Muhyeok is not here.
Where do you see him?
Hey, get out. You call that driving?
Hey, get out! Get out.
Get out while I'm being nice!
Hey! Get out! Get out!
Sorry.
What on earth? It's just a little brat.
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
Girls should just stay home at night.
Why are you out causing trouble?
What? You're staring me down?
What are you looking at?
What are you going to do?
Why I ought to...
Where do you think you're putting your hands?
Should I break your wrists?
It's warm. Drink it.
Drink it.
You're really not going to look at me?
It's because I might wake up.
I might wake up from this dream.
I'm really scared I might wake up.
It's not a dream, Eunchae.
I'm not going to get fooled again.
If I keep fooling myself pretending it's not a dream,
that you're not a dream, then...
That's how I was able to look at you, hold your hands,
and was always fooled.
Then soon someone will say,
"Wake up, Eunchae. It's all a dream."
It's not a dream.
Yun said I've gone nuts.
He said I was going crazy.
I think he's right. I think he's right.
I can't.
Even though I'd rather look at you,
what will I do about my parents?
I can't go crazy.
I'm warm, right?
You feel it beating, don't you?
I'm here.
I'm right beside you.
What is three plus two?
Five.
How about three times eight?
24.
How about 38,824 times 21,365?
How much is that?
I don't know.
Minchae said to check on your mental abilities.
To see if you've lost your marbles or not.
I didn't bring my wallet.
Me, neither.
Sorry. Don't scan these yet.
We forgot to bring our wallets.
Muhyeok!
Hi.
Will you add mine to the pile, too? I'll pay.
Yes, sir.
Muhyeok.
What Dad's name?
Song Daecheon.
Mom's name?
Jang Haesuk.
What does Mom call all 3 of us when she's busy?
I'm fine, Minchae.
What does mom call all three of us?
3 Chaes.
You seem fine. For now. It's cold.
Mister, wear this.
Eunchae.
Let's go.
You're crazy! You're going crazy again!
Why would you take that off? Are you Santa?
He's shaking because he's cold.
I have lots of clothes at home.
Crazy, crazy! Why take it off?
I told you to stay warm. Why won't you listen?
Stay warm, too, Blockhead's sister.
That was really him, right? You saw him too, right?
Yeah.
I understand Sukchae, all of a sudden.
He's definitely hot.
Galchi!
Give your uncle a hot bun, too! It's so cold!
Are you still mad because I yelled at your mom?
It's because I don't have much time.
If I had time, I would teach her 10, 20, or 100 times.
But I don't have the time.
I don't have time to teach her 10 or 100 times.
Why don't you have time?
There are 24 hours in one day.
It's too cold out.
I'm going to turn into an icicle!
I'm going to run home first.
Grandpa.
What?
Why are you wearing the worried
face of a 70-year-old man?
Uncle is a little...
Uncle is what?
Our uncle is going to die, I think.
What are you talking about out of the blue?
Yesterday, when Yun's mom came,
he told her he'd give it to her
before he died, so for her not to
act like she owed him something.
Huh?
And he also said that he didn't
have the time to teach mom
the same thing 10, 100 times.
What's going to happen if Uncle dies, Grandpa?
No way. He won't.
Your uncle is not even 30. He's still really young.
How would he suddenly die?
Don't worry. That won't happen.
Uncle.
Uncle. Wake up. Wake up.
Mom! Mom! Mom, I think Uncle is dead.
Uncle, wake up.
Yun said he won't take it.
He'd rather die and not take Muhyeok's.
Did Yun really like Muhyeok?
Maybe that's why
I can't help but like Muhyeok.
The more I see him, each time we meet.
Muhyeok. His family, too.
As if I've known them for a very long time.
I think it's because I'm old.
I'm going to leave it up to fate.
If something happens to Yun, I'll go, too.
I'll go with him.
What, Galchi?
Uncle what?
Stop crying and tell me.
What happened to your uncle?
Uncle...
What if he doesn't wake up?
Galchi.
- Mom, what are we are going to do?
- Uncle.
[Cha Muhyeok]
- Uncle. / - Uncle, wake up.
Uncle...
What are you going to do?
Uncle!
Eunchae.
He fell down, and we cried...
Muhyeok fainted.
He's in bad shape.
The doctors say he might not make
it past the next couple weeks.
Are you scared?
I got shot at my wife's wedding.
The bullet was lodged in a place
too dangerous to remove.
The bullet is right here.
Scary, huh?
Will you look after Seo-kyeong and Galchi
later when I'm gone?
Eunchae is going nuts.
We...
No, you and I have driven her insane.
It was better when we didn't do anything for her.
There was so much I wanted to give you.
But I've only given you pain.
I have nothing to give but that.
The only thing you can give to Eunchae is pain.
Let her go.
[Cha Muhyeok]
I'm shocked you're calling me.
What's going on?
Mister.
What's wrong? What happened? What happened, Muhyeok?
Take me somewhere.
In your condition? Where could I take you?
You can't go anywhere like this.
Anywhere.
Somewhere far from Seoul.
Take me somewhere far from here.
Take me.
Please.
Mister.
I'm your son too!
You gave birth to me just like you did Yun!
I'm your blood too!
Let me just see your face before I go.
I'll just see your face before I leave.
I said don't talk about him!